# Giorgi Sheklashvili

### Profile

Blockchain and decentralized technologies enthusiast with 4 years of experience in full-stack development and a master's degree in Software engineering from the University of Tartu, Estonia.

Smart contract development experience from hobby projects and master's thesis.

Experience of leading the project and reviewing code. Also, giving guidance and advices to junior developers.

Code written during employment is not publicly available but I can show it from my laptop if needed.

# Employment History

## Full-Stack Developer at TX - Tomorrow Explored, Helsinki

October 2020 — Present

• Kraken - Implemented privacy preserving data marketplace backend on Express.js, MongoDb and AWS.

Integrated with marketplace smart contract on Gnosis chain.

Used Self-sovereign identity (SSI) and DID for registration and login. Project Website

Tech Stack: Express.js, MongoDB, AWS, Truffle, Solidity, Fabric, ReactJS, Self-Sovereign identity(SSI), Decentralized identifier(DID), Multi party computation(MPC)

• Tracey - Implemented a full stack with android application, Spring boot, and Postgres database. Also, Integration with a smart contract on Ethereum testnet with web3j. Tech stack: Android, Spring Boot, PostgreSQL, Solidity, web3j

#### Article

### Software Developer at Hansab IT Solutions, Tallinn

January 2019 — September 2020

•Implemented integration with EWS and Google calendar. Implemented RFID card authentication.

Tech stack: Spring boot, Thymeleaf, Vanilla JavaScript, jQuery, Websockets, H2, Putty, WinSCP, LDAP

•Created Gradle script for assembling Jar files.

Tech stack: Spring boot, Angular

### Software developer Intern at Ignite, Tallinn

June 2018 — October 2018

- Created Role-based Authentication and PDF generation functionalities
- Tech stack: Spring boot, Vue.js, MongoDB, Docker, JUnit, Mocha,
  Chai, Velocity

#### **Details**

Helsinki

Finland

+3584578310171

sheklashviligiorgi@gmail.com

#### Links

Github

LinkedIn

### Skills

Solidity

Hardhat

**IPFS** 

Node.js

 ${\sf MongoDB}$ 

**AWS** 

Docker

React.js

Spring boot

Sef-sovereign identity

Decentralized identifier

Multi-party computation

# **Y** Extra-curricular activities

### EthGlobal HackFS, Remote

July 2021 — August 2021

Implemented pinning of multimedia files on IPFS using Textile for project called RoyaltyFreeNfts

Github

### **ReEntrancy Attack Simulation**

April 2022 — April 2022

Github

### **Upgradable contracts**

April 2022 — April 2022

Github

### **Lottery smart contract**

November 2021 — November 2021

Github

#### **ERC20 & ICO contracts**

December 2021 — December 2021

Github

### **Fundraising contract**

November 2021 — November 2021

Github

#### **Auction contract**

November 2021 — November 2021

Github

# Education

## MsC, University of Tartu, Estonia

September 2017 — July 2020

Master's thesis